<!DOCTYPE html>
<html>
<head>
    <title>Jumbo Josh - Garten of Banban</title>
    <style>
        body {
            font-family: Arial, sans-serif;
            background-color: #f0f0f0;
            color: #333;
            margin: 0;
            padding: 0;
        }

        h1 {
            text-align: center;
            margin: 20px 0;
        }

        #jumbo-josh-image {
            display: block;
            margin: 0 auto;
            width: 400px;
            height: 400px;
        }

        #description {
            text-align: center;
            font-size: 18px;
            margin: 20px 0;
        }

        #gameplay {
            max-width: 800px;
            margin: 20px auto;
            padding: 20px;
            background-color: #fff;
            border: 1px solid #ddd;
            border-radius: 10px;
        }

        #gameplay h2 {
            margin-top: 0;
            color: #007bff;
        }

        #gameplay ul {
            list-style-type: disc;
            padding-left: 20px;
        }

        #gameplay li {
            margin-bottom: 10px;
        }
    </style>
</head>
<body>
    <h1>Jumbo Josh - Garten of Banban</h1>
    <img id="jumbo-josh-image" src="jumbo_josh.jpg" alt="Jumbo Josh">
    <div id="description">
        <p>Jumbo Josh is a lime, muscular creature, vaguely shaped like a humanoid with two stubby legs, two widening forearms ending with mitten-like fists, and a rather bulbous head. On his head, there are two bugged-out eyes and a mischievous tongue-less mouth shaped into a wide grin.</p>
    </div>
    <div id="gameplay">
        <h2>Gameplay</h2>
        <p>In the game "Garten of Banban," Jumbo Josh is portrayed as a powerful and mysterious character. Here are some key moments involving him:</p>
        <ul>
            <li><strong>Garten Of Banban:</strong> Jumbo Josh appears as a surprise at the end of the game when the Player uses the elevator to go down. His unexpected appearance adds an element of suspense to the gameplay.</li>
            <li><strong>Garten of Banban II:</strong> Jumbo Josh makes a triumphant return, demonstrating his resilience and strength. Players encounter him in various intense situations, making the gameplay exciting and thrilling.</li>
            <li><strong>Garten of Banban III:</strong> Jumbo Josh becomes even more integral to the storyline. His presence adds depth to the narrative, and the player must navigate through challenges involving him and other characters.</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Jumbo Josh's imposing presence and distinctive design make him a memorable and beloved character among players of the game "Garten of Banban."</p>
    </div>
</body>
</html>
