<!DOCTYPE html>
<html>
<head>
    <title>Jumbo Josh - Mythological Creature</title>
    <style>
        body {
            font-family: Arial, sans-serif;
            background-image: url("https://files.cults3d.com/uploaders/13865489/illustration-file/577c25a6-7ee6-40af-a3da-73e645d39bf5/ezgif-2-b987d91a47.gif");
            background-repeat: repeat;
            color: #fff;
            margin: 0;
            padding: 0;
        }

        h1 {
            text-align: center;
            margin: 20px 0;
        }

        #jumbo-josh-image {
            display: block;
            margin: 0 auto;
            width: 300px;
            height: 300px;
            border: 5px solid #fff;
            border-radius: 50%;
        }

        #description {
            text-align: center;
            font-size: 18px;
            margin: 20px 0;
        }

        #gameplay {
            max-width: 800px;
            margin: 20px auto;
            padding: 20px;
            background-color: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.7);
            border: 1px solid #ddd;
            border-radius: 10px;
        }

        #gameplay h2 {
            margin-top: 0;
            color: #007bff;
        }

        #gameplay ul {
            list-style-type: disc;
            padding-left: 20px;
        }

        #gameplay li {
            margin-bottom: 10px;
        }
    </style>
</head>
<body>
    <h1>Jumbo Josh - Mythological Creature</h1>
    <img id="jumbo-josh-image" src="https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/61MmLezjobL._AC_UF894,1000_QL80_.jpg" alt="Jumbo Josh">
    <div id="description">
        <p>Jumbo Josh is an awe-inspiring mythological creature, said to have existed since ancient times. He is depicted as a powerful being with a lime, muscular physique, two stubby legs, and two mighty forearms ending with mitten-like fists. His bulbous head features two bugged-out eyes and a mischievous, wide grin.</p>
    </div>
    <div id="gameplay">
        <h2>Gameplay</h2>
        <p>Legends of Jumbo Josh have been passed down through generations. As a mythical presence, his role in the game "Garten of Banban" is deeply entwined with the player's journey. Here are some legendary moments involving him:</p>
        <ul>
            <li><strong>Mythical Encounter:</strong> Jumbo Josh emerges as a surprise at the end of the game when the Player reaches the deepest, most hidden chamber. The sight of this ancient creature sends shivers down the player's spine.</li>
            <li><strong>Epic Resurrection:</strong> In "Garten of Banban II," it is revealed that Jumbo Josh had been crushed under the Chairlift, yet he survived and rose again, showcasing his immortal nature and resilience.</li>
            <li><strong>Guardian of Secrets:</strong> In "Garten of Banban III," Jumbo Josh plays a pivotal role as the guardian of a mystical artifact, the Givanium. His presence ensures that only the most worthy may access its power.</li>
            <li><strong>Legendary Battle:</strong> Jumbo Josh's strength is put to the test in an epic battle against Banban and Stinger Flynn. Their clash shakes the very foundations of the mythical realm.</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Jumbo Josh, the mythical powerhouse, remains an enigmatic and beloved figure in the fantastical world of "Garten of Banban."</p>
    </div>
    <div id="image-gallery">
        <h2>Gallery</h2>
        <img src="https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/61MmLezjobL._AC_UF894,1000_QL80_.jpg" alt="Jumbo Josh">
        <img src="https://static.wikia.nocookie.net/gartenofbanban/images/a/a2/Joshy.png/revision/latest?cb=20230504205650" alt="Jumbo Josh">
        <img src="https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/511rIEJmb5L._AC_UF894,1000_QL80_.jpg" alt="Jumbo Josh">
    </div>
</body>
</html>
